Wow the sky is so beautiful I wish
Bartleby my lover was here to see this
did somebody say my name
this here is Bartleby my pixie lover the
sexiest of all the Pixies in the lens
although we Pixies are only five inches
tall his butt is huge as what is so big
I just want to squeeze it yes my bottom
is quite plump and dashing isn't it what
can I say
in colleges my lover look up to the sky
the stars twinkle with much grace and
beauty
much like your pixie butt yes I see they
do my pixie huh what is that
falling from above do you see that my
Beach oh my it's snowing come Bartleby
we cannot have you catch a cold let us
fly below the trees then I can make you
some fresh warm tea with some dewdrops I
gathered from the leaves and hmmm
peasant idea my Beach well then let us
be off
here is your tea Bart levy I prepared it
with love then what are you waiting for
Beach handed over I don't have all day
yes Bart lobby drink up you sexy sexy
man hey I supposed I might as well
glug glug glug what is this Beach
did I not tell you I will only drink tea
made from the finest berries picked from
the northern woods Oh Bartleby him so
sorry
please give me another chance I am
embarrassed to even look at this D cup
anymore get it away from me get it away
now Bartleby please calm down you're
making me cry you crying I should be the
one crying was I not the one who
was just served calm honesty clean this
mess up
God damn it what did I do to
deserve this
yes Bart lovey as you say Bart lovey ha
look up there my lover the snow is
falling through the leaves
Oh whatever shall we do we don't have
any shelter here actually my sexy Beach
read you huh why Bartleby what on earth
could you mean this is what I mean a
blade of grass whoaa Bartleby that is
just like you to come prepared but it's
so small but we Pixies are only 5 inches
tall there's no way it could cover two
of us it could if we touch bodies Oh Oh
Bart lovey oh yes now my Beach turn
around so I can spank your pixie s like
the little pixie you are mine now
those are some delicious looking butt
cheeks ta ithi Oh Bart lobby in blushing
look at that my Beach your bottom Peaks
hair turned red like a winter strawberry